It's time for a teaching moment.
So this is the real Al Nett.
And in response to my comments about Jasmine Crockett being a supporter of Israeli Zionism
and an establishment Democrat, thus she is not a progressive candidate and actually will
not garner my support or anyone else who does not support those things.
Her response was, like this comment, if you're a Texan who can actually vote in the Texas
primaries and not just a talking head in another state who has zero voting power, I need to
see something.
Laughing face, laughing face, laughing face, laughing face.
And so I took the time, because she wrote this under my comments, I took the time to correct
her because she doesn't seem to grasp how civics works.
So I added, I see you've missed the memo, but the legislation that happens in states carries
over to other states.
Furthermore, Texas is one of the temples to policy movement for this administration.
Every election in every state is everyone's issue.
You have been tricked and ironically are laughing at your own ignorance.
Today is the day you can change that.
I consider that to be a very generous response.
What I didn't also add is the fact that she's running for Senate.
Okay?
She's running for the United States Senate, which is a federal position.
She will be voting on laws that affect everyone in the United States because they are federal
laws.
Now, of course, folks on this internet oftentimes do not like being corrected and they want
to stand in what they don't know.
So her very mature response was, oh, girl, STFU all the way in Calabasas, spelled incorrectly
and I also don't live there.
You're a leftist talking head, an agent of chaos at this point.
Your own governor endorsed Jasmine.
Amanda Seals, we see you limited these comments.
Ma'am, my comments are limited to those who follow me.
Second, Governor Newsom is an op.
Third, do not listen to people like this.
They don't know what they're talking about.
This person doesn't seem to grasp the way that the branches of government operate.
Again, I want to remind you that anything that takes place on the federal level affects
everybody nationally, which is why when the Supreme Court said that Roe v. Wade is no longer protected
federally and it became a state's rights issue, all of the states were able to determine whether
or not they wanted to ride or let go of it.
When it was protected federally, they had no choice.
Hope this helps.
By the way, I am very accustomed to people considering me insufferable because I have no problem
correcting them and doing so while being beautiful.
Be blessed, Daryl Annette.
Like I said, today is a day you can change.